speechpad.com 2016-12-21

# Privacy Policy | Speechpad

Thank you for visiting the Speechpad website. Please review the following terms and conditions regarding your use of this website and services.

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our website, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our website, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, email address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our website anonymously.

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * **To personalize your experience** —Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.
  * **To improve our website** —We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and  
feedback we receive from you.
  * **To improve customer service** —Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service  
requests and support needs.
  * **To process transactions** —Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  * **To send periodic emails** —The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.

## Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a website or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the website’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about website traffic and website interaction so that we can offer better website experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our website visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our website policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party websites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked websites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our website and welcome any feedback about these websites.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our website may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into and editing information on the ’My Account’ page.

## Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

## Your Consent

By using our website, you consent to our website privacy policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on 1/15/2010.

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at [support@speechpad.com](mailto:support@speechpad.com).
